freedom.ws 2019-05-15

# 

                                                  Privacy Policy
Effective: 25-MAY-2018
Global Domains International, Inc., a California corporation ("GDI" or "we" or "us"), provides registration
services for the ".WS" upper level domain name in addition to services through www.WebSite.ws ("our
site" or "the site") and is committed to implementing measures designed to protect the privacy of those
using its services.
SUMMARY POLICY
Information may collect:
        Name
        Email Address
        Physical Address
        Social Security or Tax ID Number
        Phone Number
        Payment information such as credit cards or PayPal address
        Ip address
        Browser, Operating system, and Device used to access site
How information may be collected:
        The above information may be collected while browsing and using our websites
        Tax form submissions related to commissions earned
How Information is used:
        Merchant processing for purchase transactions
        Contact data for domain registrations
        Analytics and Marketing tracking of non-personally identifiable information such as pages viewed
         with Google, Facebook, and/or Twitter
How Information is stored:
        On-premises digital storage
        Browser Cookies
Individuals' Rights
        The  right to be informed on data collected by Global Domains International, Inc.
        The  right of access to data collected
        The  right to have information corrected
        The  right to erasure of information collected
        The  right to restrict processing of information collected
        The  right to data portability of the information collected
        The  right to object to information collected
        The  right not to be subject to automated decision-making including profiling

DETAILED POLICY
We collect information from users, Independent Affiliates, and Members of our site (hereafter collectively
“users”). Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use, the Terms of Service, the
Affiliate Agreement, and other published guidelines, we do not release or share personally identifiable
information about users without their permission.
Please note that we review and modify our privacy practices from time to time, and that those practices
are therefore subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure
continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. We will notify registered users
(Members and Affiliates) of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by email to the last known email
addresses of such users. To contact us about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at
privacy@wsdomains.ws.
The information we gather and how we use it
We gather two types of information about the users of our site: non-personally identifiable and personally
identifiable information. When visitors come to our site, we may collect and aggregate non-personally
identifiable information indicating, among other things, which pages were visited, the order in which they
were visited, and which hyperlinks were clicked. Collecting such information involves the logging of IP
addresses, operating system and browser software used by each visitor to the site. Although such
information is not personally identifiable, we can determine from the IP address a visitor's Internet
Service Provider and the geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.
The non-personally identifiable information we collect helps us, among other things, to monitor our
internal operations, improve our services, identify the most popular areas of our site and determine the
effectiveness of our services and promotional activities. It also helps us make available quality, more
useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of
the users of our site, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of our site.
We provide statistical information based on this data to advertisers, affiliates, and other current and
potential promotional partners.
We may also use cookies which allow us to serve visitors of our site better and more efficiently. Cookies
are small text files placed on a visitor’s computer’s hard drive if permitted by the browser. Cookies,
among other things, make it easier for users to access our site and services, and help us track the pages
that visitors go to, determine the length of time visitors spend at any particular area of the site, and track
the services visitors choose to use. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable
to read data from hard disks, execute any code, send you viruses or destroy your files. For information
on how and whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser, please refer to the documentation
accompanying your browser.
We do not collect any information that personally identifies you unless you knowingly and willingly
provide it. We explicitly ask for information that personally identifies you. For example, when registering
for a personal account, we require that you provide us with certain personally identifiable information
ranging from basic contact information to payment information to the technical coordinates of your host
servers.
As a Member or an independent Affiliate, you may choose to "opt-in" to receiving promotional materials
not directly related to services provided by us and our affiliates, advertisers, or other business partners. If
you do "opt-in" to receiving such promotional materials, we reserve the right to share any personally
identifiable registration information regarding you to third parties who provide goods or services that we
believe may be of interest to you, whether from outside vendors and/or our own offerings. If you decide
that you would like to discontinue receiving such promotional information, please contact said third
parties directly, or contact us at privacy@wsdomains.ws and we will advise said third parties that you

wish to discontinue receiving their promotional information. Note, however, that we cannot and do not
assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which
they use information received either from GDI or independently. We use personally identifiable
information to operate this site, and we may occasionally inform you by email, telephone, fax (facsimile),
text message (SMS/MMS), and/or social networking sites (e.g. - Facebook, Twitter) of new features,
services, promotions and products available on this site offered by us and our promotional partners. We
limit our own solicitations to those registered users (Affiliates, or Members) who have "opted-in" to
receiving such communications. Our solicitations are limited in that they, among other things, will clearly
indicate the sender and provide the customer with a method of "opting out" of receiving future
communications of a similar nature. If you decide that you would like to discontinue receiving information
from us about new features, services, promotions and products; or that you would like to reverse a prior
opt-out designation; please contact us at privacy@wsdomains.ws.
We reserve the right to disclose information contained within our access logs concerning any user as we
reasonably feel is necessary to protect our systems or business. Specifically, but without limitation, we
reserve the right to disclose such when a user is in violation of our Terms of Use, Terms of Service (if
applicable), the Affiliate Agreement (if applicable), or other published guidelines, or if a user partakes (or
is reasonably suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other
court order, and to disclose such information in response to court and governmental orders, civil
subpoenas, discovery requests, and as otherwise required by law. We cooperate with law enforcement
agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also
reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or
prosecution, or to suspend or terminate your membership in connection with any suspected illegal
activity. Additionally, we reserve the right to disclose the name of the registered owner and such owner’s
registered .WS domain name registered to third parties and in our promotional materials.
Changing personal information
You have the ability to change or delete your information in our records, please contact us at
privacy@wsdomains.ws.
